Guide to the J. E. Wallace Sterling, President of Stanford University, Papers
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Series 1
  - Scholarships - Latin American Scholarship Program of American Universities, 1966-1967 (Box B19, Folder 32)
  - Scholarships - Milton J. Lear Scholarship Fund, 1965-1967 (Box B19, Folder 33)
  - Scholarships - John T. Leddy Memorial Scholarship, 1955-1962 (Box B19, Folder 34)
  - Scholarships - Mortimer C. Leventritt Scholarship Award Fund, 1952-1965 (Box B19, Folder 35)
  - Scholarships - John G. Locke, Jr. Memorial Scholarship, 1956 (Box B19, Folder 36)
  - Scholarships - Juliet Lee Knopp Lickwood Memorial Fund, 1944-1962 (Box B19, Folder 37)
  - Scholarships - Lockheed Leadership Fund Scholarships, 1953-1967 (Box B19, Folder 38)
    Also see Gross-Lockheed
  - Scholarships - Robert M. and Katherine F. Loeser Scholarship in Chemistry, 1947-1956 (Box B19, Folder 39)
  - Scholarships - John Stewart Low Scholarship in Electrical Engineering, 1933-1968 (Box B19, Folder 40)
  - Scholarships - Anita Oliver Lunn Foundation Fund, 1963-1967 (Box B19, Folder 41)
  - Scholarships - Marian Wheeler Lyman Scholarship, 1955-1956 (Box B19, Folder 42)
  - Scholarships - "M", 1962-1967 (Box B19, Folder 43)
  - Scholarships - MacAlpine Scholarship Fund, 1957-1967 (Box B19, Folder 44)
  - Scholarships - Marshall Scholarship Committee (Box B19, Folder 45)
    Not a file - cross-reference to Sterlings personal file and also see Committee files - External Awards
  - Scholarships - Louis B. Mayer Scholarship Fund, 1966 (Box B19, Folder 46)
  - Scholarships - George H. Mayr Educational Foundation Scholarship Fund, 1958-1967 (Box B19, Folder 47)
  - Scholarships - Floyd L. McElroy Investment Counsel Scholarship, 1955-1962 (Box B19, Folder 48)
  - Scholarships - McMahan Foundation Scholarships, 1957-1967 (Box B19, Folder 49)
    Jessie R. McMahan included
  - Scholarships - Medical School Scholarships, 1966-1967 (Box B19, Folder 50)
  - Scholarships - Metteer Law Scholarship, 1955 (Box B19, Folder 51)
  - Scholarships - Julian J. and Adele H. Meyer Scholarship Fund, 1950-1965 (Box B19, Folder 52)
  - Scholarships - John Pearce Mitchell Scholarship Fund, 1945-1963 (Box B19, Folder 53)
  - Scholarships - Mobil Oil Company Scholarship, 1961-1965 (Box B19, Folder 54)
  - Scholarships - Robert S. and Florence Moore Scholarship, 1925-1960 (Box B19, Folder 55)
  - Scholarships - Nathaniel Richard Morgan Honors Scholarship Fund, 1942 (Box B19, Folder 56)
  - Scholarships - Henry M. Mosher Scholarship (Signal Oil and Gas Compnay), 1954-1964 (Box B19, Folder 57)
  - Scholarships - Mu of Gamma Phi Beta Scholarship Fund, 1953-1966 (Box B19, Folder 58)
  - Scholarships - Fred R. Muhrs, Jr. Scholarship Fund #1, 1953-1955 (Box B19, Folder 59)
    Also see Muhrs Fund #2
  - Scholarships - Music Guild Scholarship, 1956 (Box B19, Folder 60)
  - Scholarships - "N", 1958-1968 (Box B19, Folder 61)
    List of "N" names on outside of folder
  - Scholarships - Napa Valley Stanford Club Scholarship, 1967 (Box B19, Folder 62)
  - Scholarships - Lee and Vida Narver Scholarship Fund, 1953-1959 (Box B19, Folder 63)
  - Scholarships - Henry Newell Scholarship Fund, 1929-1965 (Box B19, Folder 64)
  - Scholarships - New Hampshire Charitable Fund Scholarship, 1965 (Box B19, Folder 65)
    Spaulding-Potter Charitable Trusts
  - Scholarships - Douglas E. Newton Scholarship, 1937-1968 (Box B19, Folder 66)
  - Scholarships - William H. Nichols Scholarship Fund, 1951-1963 (Box B19, Folder 67)
    Gift of Madeline Nichols Sharp
  - Scholarships - "O", 1956-1968 (Box B19, Folder 68)
    List of "O" names on outside of folder
  - Scholarships - Owens-Illinois Scholarship Fund, 1956-1968 (Box B19, Folder 69)
  - Scholarships - "P", 1961-1966 (Box B19, Folder 70)
    List of "P" names on outside of folder
  - Scholarships - Mary Louise Palmer Scholarship, 1958-1960 (Box B19, Folder 71)
  - Scholarships - Olive and Silas Palmer Honors Scholarship Fund, 1935-1967 (Box B19, Folder 72)
  - Scholarships - Stanley Pedder Law Scholarship Fund, 1955-1957 (Box B19, Folder 73)
  - Scholarships - Pfizer Laboratory Medical Scholarship, 1963-1967 (Box B19, Folder 74)
  - Scholarships - John Pressley Phillips Memorial Scholarship, 1941-1968 (Box B19, Folder 75)
  - Scholarships - Pregnoff and Matheu Company Scholarship, 1964 (Box B19, Folder 76)
  - Scholarships - Proctor and Gamble Scholarships, 1955-1968 (Box B19, Folder 77)
  - Scholarships - Longueville and Marjorie Price Scholarship, 1944-1961 (Box B19, Folder 78)
  - Scholarships - George M. Pullman Educational Foundation Scholarship, 1955-1967 (Box B19, Folder 79)
  - Scholarships, 1956-1968 (Box B19, Folder 80)
    List of "R" names on outside of folder
  - Scholarships - William R. Ray Scholarship Fund, 1955-1963 (Box B19, Folder 81)
  - Scholarships - Raynier Foundation Scholarship Fund, 1956-1967 (Box B19, Folder 82)
  - Scholarships - Frank Rehm Scholarship Fund, 1955-1966 (Box B19, Folder 83)
  - Scholarships - Leon B. Reynolds Memorial Fund, 1955-1965 (Box B19, Folder 84)
  - Scholarships - Mabel Wilson Richards Scholarship, 1952-1968 (Box B19, Folder 85)
  - Scholarships - Mary Foster Riotte Scholarship in History, 1947-1951 (Box B19, Folder 86)
  - Scholarships - John J. Rogers Scholarship Fund, 1952-1962 (Box B19, Folder 87)
  - Scholarships - Roble Club Scholarship, 1932-1961 (Box B19, Folder 88)
  - Scholarships - Henry E. Rosin Memorial Scholarship Fund, 1958-1962 (Box B19, Folder 89)
  - Scholarships - Rosalie Meyer Stern Scholarship Fund, 1955-1968 (Box B20, Folder 1)
  - Scholarships - William W. Stout Scholarship Fund, 1958-1960 (Box B20, Folder 2)
  - Scholarships - "T", 1956-1968 (Box B20, Folder 3)
  - Scholarships - The Texas Company Scholarships (Texaco), 1956-1967 (Box B20, Folder 4)
  - Scholarships - Harry A. True Memorial Scholarship, 1951-1962 (Box B20, Folder 5)
  - Scholarships - "U", 1961-1968 (Box B20, Folder 6)
  - Scholarships - Uniroyal, Inc., 1967-1968 (Box B20, Folder 7)
  - Scholarships - United California Bank, 1957-1967 (Box B20, Folder 8)
  - Scholarships - University Honors Scholarships (Graduate and Undergraduate), 1948-1966 (Box B20, Folder 9)
  - Scholarships - "V", 1960-1965 (Box B20, Folder 10)
  - Scholarships - Stanley Wilson Vanderburgh Memorial Scholarship, 1941-1962 (Box B20, Folder 11)
  - Scholarships - Suzanne Vinetz Memorial Scholarship, 1952-1968 (Box B20, Folder 12)
  - Scholarships - Royal Victor Scholarship, 1961-1965 (Box B20, Folder 13)
  - Scholarships - Helen Bennett Voorhees Memorial Scholarship, 1943-1962 (Box B20, Folder 14)
  - Scholarships - "W", 1955-1966 (Box B20, Folder 15)
  - Scholarships - Walter Pernau Walsh Memorial Scholarship, 1953-1958 (Box B20, Folder 16)
  - Scholarships - Clarence Almon Waring Memorial Scholarship, 1955-1957 (Box B20, Folder 17)
  - Scholarships - Elizabeth Maples Warner Memorial Scholarship, 1958-1961 (Box B20, Folder 18)
  - Scholarships - Western Electric Company Scholarship, 1956-1968 (Box B20, Folder 19)
  - Scholarships - Western Electronic Manufacturers Association Scholarship, 1952-1967 (Box B20, Folder 20)
  - Scholarships - James Birdsall Weter Memorial Honors Scholarship, 1939-1961 (Box B20, Folder 21)
  - Scholarships - Weyerhaeuser Timber Foundation Scholarship Fund, 1955-1965 (Box B20, Folder 22)
  - Scholarships - John H. and Elliott H. Wheeler Scholarship and Fellowship Fund, 1956-1968 (Box B20, Folder 23)
    Estate of Elliott H. Wheeler
  - Scholarships - Emil Wickman Scholarship, 1954-1956 (Box B20, Folder 24)
    Also see Wickman Endowment Fund
  - Scholarships - Wilbur-Ellis Company Scholarship, 1944-1953 (Box B20, Folder 25)
  - Scholarships - Women's Recreation Association, 1943-1959 (Box B20, Folder 26)
  - Scholarships - Women's Residence Summer Club Scholarship, 1953-1957 (Box B20, Folder 27)
  - Scholarships - Women's Row Honors Scholarship, 1949-1956 (Box B20, Folder 28)
  - Scholarships - Woodbury Scholarship, 1954-1967 (Box B20, Folder 29)
  - Scholarships - Bernice and Walter Wright Scholarship, 1950-1962 (Box B20, Folder 30)
    Established by Mrs. W. P. Fuller, Jr.
  - Scholarships - Hobart N. Young Scholarship Fund, 1961-1965 (Box B20, Folder 31)
  - Scholarships - Young and Rubicam Scholarship Fund, 1961-1963 (Box B20, Folder 32)
  - Scholarships - Mary Yost Scholarship, 1941-1965 (Box B20, Folder 33)
  - Scholarships - Richard C. and J. D. Zellerbach, 1952-1968 (Box B20, Folder 34)
  - Committees - Academic Council, 1944-1948 (Box B21, Folder 1)
  - Committees - Academic Council Membership, 1944-1945 (Box B21, Folder 2)
  - Committees - Academic Council Executive Committee, 1960-1966 (Box B21, Folder 3)
  - Committees - Academic Council Committee on the Graduate Division, 1960-1966 (Box B21, Folder 4)
  - Committees - Academic Council Registrar's Advisory Committee, 1960-1966 (Box B21, Folder 5)
  - Committees - Academic Council Committee on Housing Policy, 1962 (Box B21, Folder 6)
  - Committees - Academic Council Committee on Research Policy, 1966 (Box B21, Folder 7)
  - Committees - Academic Council Committee on Teacher Education, 1960-1966 (Box B21, Folder 8)
  - Committees - Academic Council Committee on Undergraduate Education, 1963-1965 (Box B21, Folder 9)
  - Committees - Academic Council Committee on University Libraries, 1960-1966 (Box B21, Folder 10)
  - Committees - Academic Council Ad Hoc Undergraduate Library Committee, 1962 (Box B21, Folder 11)
  - Committees - Academic Council Committee on University Publications, 1960-1966 (Box B21, Folder 12)
  - Committees - Academic Council Worksheets Committee, 1962-1966 (Box B21, Folder 13)
  - Committees - Academic Council Ad Hoc Rushing Committee, 1965-1966 (Box B21, Folder 14)
  - Committees - Undergraduate Admissions, 1964-1966 (Box B21, Folder 15)
  - Committees - Sub-Committee on General Studies, 1965 (Box B21, Folder 16)
    Part of Committee on Advision
  - Committees - African Studies, 1962-1964 (Box B21, Folder 17)
  - Committees - Architectural Advisory Council, 1961-1962 (Box B21, Folder 18)
  - Committees - Athletic Meeting, 1964-1966 (Box B21, Folder 19)
    Regarding AAU-NCAA
  - Committees - Athletic Committee, 1960-1966 (Box B21, Folder 20)
  - Committees - Audio-Visual Aids, 1946-1950 (Box B21, Folder 21)
  - Committees - California Advisory Committee - Press, 1945 (Box B21, Folder 22)
  - Committees - Cancer Research, 1955-1963 (Box B21, Folder 23)
  - Committees - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace - Steering Committee, 1956-1959 (Box B21, Folder 24)
  - Committees - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace - Steering Committee, 1955-1956 (Box B21, Folder 25)
  - Committees - Chaplan's Advisory, 1946-1949 (Box B21, Folder 26)
  - Committees - Commission on Education and International Affairs - American Council on Education, 1960-1962 (Box B21, Folder 27)
  - Committees - Committee on Community Health Planning, 1964-1965 (Box B21, Folder 28)
  - Committees - Joint Meeting of the Committee on University Policy and the Advisory Board, 1965 (Box B21, Folder 29)
  - Committees - Computer Planning, 1965 (Box B21, Folder 30)
  - Committees - Consulting Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1965-1966 (Box B21, Folder 31)
  - Committees - Department of Commerce, 1942-1943 (Box B21, Folder 32)
    Paul Hanna included
  - Committees - Editorial Advisory, 1960-1961 (Box B21, Folder 33)
    Includes Stanford Today, 1963-1964
  - Committees - Eisenhower Presidential Library, California Committee, 1959 (Box B21, Folder 34)
  - Committees - Consulting Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1944-1946 (Box B21, Folder 35)
  - Committees - Electron Microscope Committee, 1944-1948 (Box B21, Folder 36)
  - Committees - Faculty Club Planning, 1961-1962 (Box B22, Folder 1)
  - Committees - Faculty Committee on Stanford Alumni Conference, 1964-1965 (Box B22, Folder 2)
  - Committees - Faculty Committee to Prepare Memorial Resolution in Honor of Dr. Timoshenko, 1965 (Box B22, Folder 3)
  - Committees - Financial Aid (Student), 1961-1966 (Box B22, Folder 4)
  - Committees - Financial Awards (External), 1965-1966 (Box B22, Folder 5)
  - Committees - Committee on Financial Awards (External), 1965 (Box B22, Folder 6)
  - Committees - Financial Awards (External), 1960-1965 (Box B22, Folder 7)
  - Committees - Ford Scholarship Committee, 1952-1960 (Box B22, Folder 8)
  - Committees - Foreign Student Scholarship Committee - ASSU Special Committee, 1961-1963 (Box B22, Folder 9)
  - Committees - Foreign Visitors and Students, 1960-1964 (Box B22, Folder 10)
  - Committees - General Motors Scholarship Committee, 1955-1965 (Box B22, Folder 11)
  - Committees - Committee on International Study, 1947-1948 (Box B22, Folder 12)
  - Committees - International Studies, 1960-1965 (Box B22, Folder 13)
  - Committees - Subcommittee on Libraries of the Committee on International Studies, 1963-1965 (Box B22, Folder 14)
  - Committees - Independent Study Committee, 1944-1946 (Box B22, Folder 15)
  - Committees - Graduate School for Public Service, 1942-1943 (Box B22, Folder 16)
    Dealings with Paul Hanna and Harold Jacobs
  - Committees - Graduate School for Public Service, 1943 (Box B22, Folder 17)
    Dealings with Harold Jacobs and Paul Hanna
  - Committees - Latin American Studies, 1944-1950 (Box B22, Folder 18)
  - Committees - Latin American Studies, 1963-1966 (Box B22, Folder 19)
  - Committees - Land and Building Development, 1963-1966 (Box B22, Folder 20)
    Includes Subcommittee on Faculty Housing
  - Committees - Library Development Fund, 1960-1961 (Box B22, Folder 21)
  - Committees - Marshall Scholarships, 1952-1955 (Box B22, Folder 22)
  - Committees - Marshall Scholarship, 1955-1956 (Box B22, Folder 23)
  - Committees - Marshall Scholarship, 1958-1964 (Box B22, Folder 24)
  - Committees - Marshall Scholarship, 1962-1967 (Box B22, Folder 25)
  - Committees - Medical School - Clinical Committee, 1947-1949 (Box B22, Folder 26)
  - Committees - Medical School - Clinical Committee, 1963-1965 (Box B22, Folder 27)
  - Committees - Medical School - Executive Committee, 1964-1968 (Box B22, Folder 28)
  - Committees - Medical School - Executive Committee, 1963-1965 (Box B22, Folder 29)
  - Committees - Medical School - Committee on Admissions, 1963-1966 (Box B22, Folder 30)
  - Committees - Medical School - miscellaneous, 1943-1946 (Box B22, Folder 31)
    List of Committees on outside of folder
  - Committees - National Foundation - Committee on Professional Education, 1954-1962 (Box B23, Folder 1)
  - Committees - PACE Advisory Committee, 1963-1964 (Box B23, Folder 2)
  - Committees - Planning Coordinating, 1966 (Box B23, Folder 3)
  - Committees - Commission on Presidential Scholars, 1966-1967 (Box B23, Folder 4)
  - Committees - President's Student Advisory Committee, 1963-1966 (Box B23, Folder 5)
  - Committees - President's Student-Faculty Committee, 1960-1962 (Box B23, Folder 6)
  - Committees - Press Administrative Committee, 1945 (Box B23, Folder 7)
  - Committees - Prizes for Academic Distinction (Achievement and Leadership), 1956-1960 (Box B23, Folder 8)
  - Committees - East Asian Studies, Provost's Special Committee, 1962 (Box B23, Folder 9)
  - Committees - Public Health, 1960-1965 (Box B23, Folder 10)
  - Committees - Public Roads Administration, 1942-1943 (Box B23, Folder 11)
  - Committees - Radio, Special Committee, 1944-1951 (Box B23, Folder 12)
  - Committees - Committee on Radio, TV and Motion Pictures, 1960-1966 (Box B23, Folder 13)
  - Committees - Registrars Advisory Committee, 1966 (Box B23, Folder 14)
  - Committees - Committee on Rehabiltation, 1943-1944 (Box B23, Folder 15)
  - Committees - Religious Affairs, 1964-1966 (Box B23, Folder 16)
  - Committees - Residence Operating Committee, 1966 (Box B23, Folder 17)
  - Committees - Rhodes Scholarship, 1953-1966 (Box B23, Folder 18)
  - Committees - Rhodes Scholarship Trust, 1959-1960 (Box B23, Folder 19)
  - Committees - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Inc. - Special Studies Project - Subpanel V, 1956-1961 (Box B23, Folder 20)
  - Committees - Scholarship, 1943-1948 (Box B24, Folder 1)
  - Committees - Committee on Statistics, 1944-1948 (Box B24, Folder 2)
  - Committees - SLAC Coordinating Committee, 1963-1966 (Box B24, Folder 3)
  - Committees - Stanford in Tokyo, 1960-1962 (Box B24, Folder 4)
  - Committees - Stanford Center in Hong Kong, 1957-1961 (Box B24, Folder 5)
    Also see Teipe
  - Committees - Stanford Center in Teipei, 1960-1962 (Box B24, Folder 6)
  - Committees - Stanford Today and Tomorrow, 1966 (Box B24, Folder 7)
  - Committees - Stanford Union, 1961-1962 (Box B24, Folder 8)
  - Committees - General Studies Abroad - Japan, 1958-1959 (Box B24, Folder 9)
  - Committees - Commission for Student Aid, 1942-1945 (Box B24, Folder 10)
  - Committees - Commission for Student Aid, 1940-1941 (Box B24, Folder 11)
  - Committees - Commission for Student Aid, 1941-1942 (Box B24, Folder 12)
  - Committees - Commission for Student Aid, 1946-1947 (Box B24, Folder 13)
  - Committees - Student Affairs and Services, 1964-1965 (Box B24, Folder 14)
  - Committees - Student Advisory Committee on Student Publications, 1965-1966 (Box B24, Folder 15)
  - Committees - Ad Hoc Committee on Student Publications, 1965 (Box B24, Folder 16)
  - Committees - Student Residences, 1957-1960 (Box B24, Folder 17)
  - Committees - Summer Festival, 1964-1965 (Box B24, Folder 18)
  - Committees - Summer Session, 1960-1961 (Box B24, Folder 19)
  - Committees - Subcommittee on Foreign Languages, 1965 (Box B24, Folder 20)
  - Committees - Sunday Activities, 1956-1966 (Box B24, Folder 21)
  - Committees - Ticket Agency, 1947-1949 (Box B24, Folder 22)
  - Committees - Undergraduate Study, 1945 (Box B24, Folder 23)
  - Committees - U.S. Advisory Commission on Educational Exchange, 1961 (Box B24, Folder 24)
  - Committees - U.S. Advisory Commission on Educational Exchange, 1960 (Box B24, Folder 25)
  - Committees - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare - National Advisory Council - Health Research Facilities, 1956-1961 (Box B24, Folder 26)
  - Committees - United States Naval Academy - Board of Visitors, 1956-1958 (Box B24, Folder 27)
  - Committees - Sterlings Naval Research Advisory Committee, 1946-1956 (Box B24, Folder 28)
  - Committees - University Service, 1942-1944 (Box B24, Folder 29)
  - Committees - Veterans' Education, 1944-1948 (Box B24, Folder 30)
  - Committees - Vice-Presidents' Committee, 1962-1965 (Box B24, Folder 31)
  - Committees - War Memorial, 1942-1948 (Box B24, Folder 32)
  - General- "A", 1962 (Box B25, Folder 1)
  - Acacdmeic Freedom and Communism, 1939-1951 (Box B25, Folder 2)
  - Merle N. Alderman, 1953 (Box B25, Folder 3)
  - American Association for the United Nations, 1955 (Box B25, Folder 4)
  - Belgian American Educational Foundation, Inc., 1955-1956 (Box B25, Folder 5)
  - Belgian American Foundation, Inc., 1964-1966 (Box B25, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Remsen DuBois Bird -, 1953-1961 (Box B25, Folder 7)
    Monterey Institute of Foreign Studies
  - Board of Governors, 1950 (Box B25, Folder 8)
  - General- "C", 1956-1966 (Box B25, Folder 9)
  - California Insitute of Technology, 1952-1966 (Box B25, Folder 10)
  - Cate Summer School of World Affairs, 1956-1966 (Box B25, Folder 11)
  - Fred Clark, 1962 (Box B25, Folder 12)
    American Economic Foundation
  - Commission for Financing a Higher Education, 1949-1950 (Box B25, Folder 13)
  - Commission for Financing a Higher Education, 1950-1952 (Box B25, Folder 14)
  - General- "D", 1964 (Box B25, Folder 15)
  - East Asian Studies, 1963-1965 (Box B25, Folder 16)
  - Equitable Life Assurance Society of the U.S., 1955-1965 (Box B25, Folder 17)
  - Ford International Fellowship Board, 1961-1965 (Box B26, Folder 1)
  - Founders Day, 1945-1950 (Box B26, Folder 2)
  - Funds "B", 1942-1955 (Box B26, Folder 3)
  - Funds "C", 1934-1963 (Box B26, Folder 4)
  - Funds "D", 1941-1962 (Box B26, Folder 5)
  - Funds "E" and "F", 1946-1953 (Box B26, Folder 6)
  - Hispanic American Report, 1960 (Box B26, Folder 7)
  - Invitations to Speak, 1951-1952 (Box B26, Folder 8)
  - Invitations, 1952 (Box B26, Folder 9)
  - Invitations - Inaugural, 1951-1952 (Box B26, Folder 10)
  - Invitations - Sterling and Student Groups, 1959-1965 (Box B26, Folder 11)
  - Invitations to Speak - Accepted, 1959-1963 (Box B26, Folder 12)
  - Invitations to Speak -Regretted, 1965-1966 (Box B26, Folder 13)
  - Invitations to Speak - Regretted, 1962-1965 (Box B26, Folder 14)
  - Invitations to Speak - Undecided, 1961 (Box B26, Folder 15)
  - Invitations, 1951-1952 (Box B26, Folder 16)
  - Invitations to Speak - Accepted, 1951-1952 (Box B26, Folder 17)
  - Honorable Kurt G. Kiesinger, 1967 (Box B26, Folder 18)
    Chancellor of West Germany
  - Loyalty Oath, 1938-1950 (Box B26, Folder 19)
  - General "M", 1952-1964 (Box B26, Folder 20)
  - General "M", 1957-1962 (Box B26, Folder 21)
  - Medical School, 1949-1950 (Box B26, Folder 22)
  - Medical Center, 1953-1961 (Box B26, Folder 23)
  - Medical School Alumni Fund, 1954-1955 (Box B26, Folder 24)
  - O'Connell Files, 1946-1950 (Box B26, Folder 25)
    Meeting minutes
  - Polytechnic School - Pasadena, 1957-1961 (Box B26, Folder 26)
  - General "S", 1949-1950 (Box B26, Folder 27)
  - Sterling Appointment, 1949 (Box B26, Folder 28)
  - Dr. J. E. Wallace Sterling, 1949 (Box B26, Folder 29)
    Notes to Dr. Sterling during his appointment as president
  - Thatcher School, 1961-1963 (Box B26, Folder 30)
  - Thatcher School, 1958-1961 (Box B26, Folder 31)
  - Thatcher School, 1954-1958 (Box B26, Folder 32)
    Sterling was a member of the Board of Trustees
  - Tulane University, 1961 (Box B27, Folder 1)
    Member of the Board of Visitors
  - Tulane University, 1961 (Box B27, Folder 2)
  - Tulane University, 1962 (Box B27, Folder 3)
  - Tulane University, 1962 (Box B27, Folder 4)
  - Tulane University, 1963 (Box B27, Folder 5)
  - Tulane University, 1964 (Box B27, Folder 6)
  - Tulane University, 1965 (Box B27, Folder 7)
  - Tulane University, 1966 (Box B27, Folder 8)
  - Tulane University, 1967 (Box B27, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Associates - Minutes of the Board of Governors, 1954-1955 (Box B28, Folder 1)
  - Academic Council Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box B28, Folder 2)
  - Committee on General Studies - Minutes, 1959-1965 (Box B28, Folder 3)
  - Advisory Committee on Land and Building Development, 1963-1965 (Box B28, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Associates - Board of Governors Minutes, 1955 (Box B29, Folder 1)
  - Committee on General Studies - Minutes, 1960-1962 (Box B29, Folder 2)
  - Associated Students of Stanford University (ASSU) Minutes, 1965 (Box B29, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Public Exercises - Minutes, 1964-1966 (Box B29, Folder 4)
  - Committee on University Policy - Minutes, 1961 (Box B29, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Committee Recommendations on Public Exercises, 1963 (Box B29, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Alumni Association, 1961-1964 (Box B29, Folder 7)
  - Speech Information, 1958-1959 (Box B30, Folder 1)
    Statistics and data on Stanford
  - National Fund for Medical Education, 1965-1967 (Box B30, Folder 2)
  - Education Commission - Study of PhD. Programs, 1966 (Box B30, Folder 3)
  - Report of the Faculty Committee on Quality of Undergraduate Instruction, 1965 (Box B30, Folder 4)
    For Cornell University
  - Undergraduate General Education in the Next Decade, 1967 (Box B30, Folder 5)
    Committee on General Studies. Revised 2nd draft
  - Committee for the Selection of an Ombudsman for Santa Clara County, 1967 (Box B30, Folder 6)
  - Committee on University Policy, 1967 (Box B30, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Association - Bakersfield Conference and Visalia Conference, 1965 (Box B30, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Association - Conference Chairmen Workshop, 1964-1965 (Box B30, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Association - San Diego/Riverside Conference, 1965 (Box B30, Folder 10)
    Notes for a speech